Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series L is arranged in 14 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LI is arranged in 2 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LII is arranged in 17 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series L. COURT DECISIONS
  - Sub-Series 316-0. Court Decisions
    - General, 1957 (Box 504, Folder 3)
      April-December 1957.
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 504, Folder 4)
      July 1956-March 1957.
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 504, Folder 5)
      September 1955-June 1956.
    - General, 1955 (Box 504, Folder 6)
      January-August 1955.
    - General, 1953-1954 (Box 504, Folder 7)
    - General, 1950-1952 (Box 504, Folder 8)
      April 1950-52.
    - General, 1947 (Box 504, Folder 9)
    - General, 1948-1950 (Box 504, Folder 10)
      1948-March 1950.
    - General, 1945-1946 (Box 505, Folder 1)
    - General, 1942-1944 (Box 505, Folder 2)
    - General. Moore vs. Illinois Central, 1941 (Box 505, Folder 3)
    - General, 1943-1944 (Box 505, Folder 4)
    - General, 1930 (Box 505, Folder 5)
    - General, 1923-1930 (Box 505, Folder 6)
    - General, 1936-1941 (Box 505, Folder 7)
      September 1936-41.
    - General, 1928 (Box 505, Folder 8)
    - General, 1927 (Box 505, Folder 9)
    - General, 1946 (Box 505, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 316-1. Court Decisions
    - United States Supreme Court, 1945-1949 (Box 505, Folder 11)
    - United States Supreme Court, 1935-1943 (Box 505, Folder 12)
    - United States Supreme Court, 1922-1925 (Box 505, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 316-2. Court Decisions
    - An Example of the Court's Boring from Within, 1921 (Box 505, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 316-3. Court Decisions
    - Mississippi, 1937-1938 (Box 505, Folder 15)
    - Mississippi, 1922 (Box 505, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 316-4. Court Decisions
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit, 1921 (Box 505, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 316-5. Court Decisions
    - Denver and Salt Lake Railroad Company (Box 505, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 316-9. Court Decisions
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1928 (Box 505, Folder 19)
      1928 May 24
    - McGinnis v. Bierd, 1929 (Box 505, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 316-10. Court Decisions
    - Minnesota, 1929 (Box 505, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 316-11. Court Decisions
    - United States District Court for California, 1930 (Box 505, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 316-12. Court Decisions
    - Kentucky, 1933 (Box 505, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 316-13. Court Decisions
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1933 (Box 505, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 316-14. Court Decisions
    - Ohio, 1934 (Box 505, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 316-15. Court Decisions
    - Circuit Court of Hinds County, Mississippi, 1934 (Box 505, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 316-16. Court Decisions
    - Oregon, 1935 (Box 505, Folder 27)
- Series LI. ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN RAILROADS
  - Sub-Series 318-0. Association of American Railroads
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 506, Folder 1)
      August 1960-62.
    - General, 1951-1960 (Box 506, Folder 2)
      1951-July 1960.
    - General, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3)
      March-December 1950.
    - General, 1945-1950 (Box 506, Folder 4)
      August 1945-February 1950.
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1945 (Box 506, Folder 5)
    - The Public Looks at Railroads, 1949 (Box 506, Folder 6)
    - General, 1944-1945 (Box 506, Folder 7)
      June 6, 1944-July 1945.
    - General, 1935-1944 (Box 506, Folder 8)
      1935-May 1944.
    - Railroad Manual on Employment Stabilization, 1943 (Box 506, Folder 9)
      1943 September
    - General, 1942 (Box 506, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 318-2. Association of American Railroads
    - Railroad Executives Association, 1922 (Box 506, Folder 11)
- Series LII. BROTHERHOOD BUILDING COMPANY
  - Sub-Series 322-0. Brotherhood Building Company
    - General, 1927 (Box 506, Folder 12)
    - General, 1932 (Box 506, Folder 13)
    - General, 1926 (Box 506, Folder 14)
    - General, 1924 (Box 506, Folder 15)
    - General, 1925 (Box 506, Folder 16)
    - General, 1929 (Box 506, Folder 17)
    - General, 1930 (Box 506, Folder 18)
    - General, 1931 (Box 506, Folder 19)
    - General, 1922-1923 (Box 506, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 322-2. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Plans, 1922 (Box 506, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 322-3. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Construction and Fixtures, 1922-1923 (Box 506, Folder 22)
    - Construction and Fixtures, 1924 (Box 506, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 322-4. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Applications for Employment, 1926-1927 (Box 506, Folder 24)
    - Applications for Employment, 1922 (Box 506, Folder 25)
    - Applications for Employment, 1924 (Box 506, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 322-5. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Rentals, 1930 (Box 507, Folder 1)
    - Rentals, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 2)
    - Rentals, 1940-1941 (Box 507, Folder 3)
    - Rentals, 1931 (Box 507, Folder 4)
    - Rentals, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 5)
    - Rentals, 1929 (Box 507, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 322-6. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Insurance, 1939-1945 (Box 507, Folder 7)
    - Insurance, 1932 (Box 507, Folder 8)
    - Insurance, 1926 (Box 507, Folder 9)
    - Insurance, 1930 (Box 507, Folder 10)
    - Insurance, 1929 (Box 507, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 322-7. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Furniture and Fixtures, 1938-1950 (Box 507, Folder 12)
      1938-January 1950.
    - Furniture and Fixtures, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 13)
    - Furniture and Fixtures, 1930-1942 (Box 507, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 322-8. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Queen City Coal Company, 1923 (Box 507, Folder 15)
      1923 August 31
  - Sub-Series 322-9. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Hatfield Campbell Creek Coal Company, 1928 (Box 507, Folder 16)
    - Hatfield Campbell Creek Coal Company, 1924 (Box 507, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 322-10. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Officers' Bonds, 1939-1942 (Box 507, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 322-12. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Taxes, 1932 (Box 507, Folder 19)
    - Taxes, 1926 (Box 507, Folder 20)
      1926 January 18
    - Taxes, 1924 (Box 507, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 322-13. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Repairs, 1926-1928 (Box 507, Folder 22)
    - Repairs, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 23)
    - Repairs, 1930 (Box 507, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 322-14. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Employees, 1930-1955 (Box 507, Folder 25)
    - Employees, 1954 (Box 507, Folder 26)
    - Employees, 1931 (Box 507, Folder 27)
    - Employees, 1926 (Box 507, Folder 28)
    - Employees, 1929 (Box 507, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 322-15. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Reinstatement of Cancelled Note, 1929 (Box 507, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 322-16. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Shareholder Meetings, 1933-1957 (Box 507, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 322-17. Brotherhood Building Company
    - Realtor, 1929 (Box 507, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 322-19. Brotherhood Building Company
    - United States Veterans Bureau, 1933 (Box 507, Folder 33)